What's up, GQ? I'm Hailey Bieber, and today I'm going undercover on the internet. It's actually me. Seriously.
大家好，GQ！我是 Hailey Bieber，今天我要在网上匿名"潜伏"一下。没错，真的是我本人。 真的。
[Reddit] Scary rabbit holes.
[Reddit] 真是些让人越看越陷进去的"兔子洞"。
"Does Hailey ever go into Justin's closet/borrow clothes?" "Hailey
会去 Justin 的衣橱里借衣服穿吗？"
Yes, all the time.
会啊，经常。
We like share each other's clothes.
我们经常互相穿对方的衣服。
I steal like sweats and tees, and the typical things that you steal from, like, a boyfriend, or a husband, or a partner.
我会"顺走"卫衣、T 恤这些，就是那种你会从男朋友、丈夫或者伴侣那里拿来穿的衣服。
So "Well, well, well, one of the ingredients in the Erewhon Hailey Bieber smoothie is sea moss gel." "
哎呀哎呀，Erewhon 的 Hailey Bieber 奶昔里的一种配料居然是海藻胶。"
And they said, "Wait, the name of the drink is the 'Glaze Skin Smoothie'? WTF."
有人说："等等，这杯饮品居然叫『Glaze Skin Smoothie』？什么情况？"
Yeah, so we did the Erewhon smoothie around the time that I was launching Rhode in 2022.
是的，我们推出这款 Erewhon 奶昔的时候，正好也是我在 2022 年推出 Rhode 品牌的时候。
It actually happened in a funny way and quite organically.
这件事其实发生得很有趣，也非常自然。
I went into Erewhon and ordered a smoothie I order all the time.
我走进 Erewhon，点了一杯我平时经常喝的奶昔。
It was strawberry, and avocado, and like all these things. And I had posted it, and then I guess a bunch of people started coming in like, "I wanna get this same thing."
里面有草莓、牛油果，还有其他一些配料。我把它发到了网上，然后我猜很多人就开始跑来点同款了。
I ended up speaking with Erewhon about potentially doing this smoothie collab that was around the same time as the Rhode launch, so it kind of coincided and went together.
后来我和 Erewhon 商量合作推出这款奶昔，时间刚好和 Rhode 上市差不多，所以两件事就自然配合到一起了。
I came with my kind of made-up recipe and worked with their team to boost it up and we added the sea moss gel for your skin, and there's hyaluronic, there's peptides, there's collagen, there's like all these things that are really good for your skin, and that is how the Strawberry Glaze Skin Smoothie was born.
我带着自己构思的配方，和他们的团队一起把它进一步优化，加入了海藻胶、透明质酸、胜肽、胶原蛋白等很多对皮肤有益的成分，这就是 Strawberry Glaze Skin Smoothie 的诞生过程。
[Wikipedia] Wikipedia  "She was named after Halley's Comet." "
[Wikipedia] 她的名字来源于哈雷彗星。"
I'm actually not 100% sure.
其实我也不是百分之百确定。
I'm gonna call my mom really quick. We'll see if she answers.
我赶紧给我妈妈打个电话，看看她接不接。
I have this recollection that she said I was moving around like Halley's Comet in her belly and that's why.
我隐约记得，她说我当时在她肚子里动来动去，就像哈雷彗星一样，所以才给我取了这个名字。
So I'm doing this interview right now. You're on speaker. A bunch of people can hear you.
我现在正在做采访，你开着免提呢，很多人都能听见你说话。
We're trying to confirm or deny, was I named after Halley's Comet?
我们想确认一下，我真的是以哈雷彗星命名的吗？
Because, well, when I was pregnant with you, you were so active in my womb, and I felt like I got hit by a comet.
因为我怀你的时候，你在子宫里特别活跃，我感觉自己就像被一颗彗星撞到了一样。
So then that is true. I'm gonna call you back in a little bit. I love you.
那这么说就是真的了。 我过一会儿再给你回电话。我爱你。
All right, love you. God bless you. Bye.
好的，爱你。愿上帝保佑你。拜拜。
Okay, bye. Well, there you go. Straight from the woman-who-birthed-me's mouth.
好，拜拜。好了，这就是答案，直接来自把我生下来那位女士本人。
Next one."Bieber's first career aspiration was to become a professional classical ballet dancer, but her training ended due to a foot injury."
下一条。"Bieber 最初的职业理想是成为一名职业古典芭蕾舞演员，但由于脚部受伤，她结束了训练。"
That's not entirely true.
这并不完全正确。
I did ballet for 12 years. I wasn't aspiring to be a professional dancer for my career.
我学了12年芭蕾。 我并没有把成为职业舞者作为自己的职业目标。
I did sustain several injuries being a dancer.
不过，跳舞期间我的确受过好几次伤。
But I stopped dancing because I started modeling when I was 16 and I never really saw myself being a ballet dancer as my whole career.
但我后来停止跳舞，是因为16岁开始做模特，而且我从来没有真正把芭蕾舞演员当作自己一生的职业。
"In addition to English, Bieber speaks some Portuguese as the maternal side of her family is Brazilian." "
除了英语之外，Bieber 还会说一些葡萄牙语，因为她母亲这一边的家族来自巴西。"
That is true. My mom is born in Brazil. She was born in Rio. And I can speak a little bit of Portuguese, and I wish that I could speak it fluently.
这是真的。 我妈妈出生在巴西。 她出生在里约。 我会说一点葡萄牙语，但我希望自己能够说得很流利。
[Instagram] Instagram.  So this is a picture that I posted with our new MagSafe lip holder, and the comment says, "So now a lippie holder for every surface."
[Instagram] 这是我发的一张照片，展示了我们的新款 MagSafe 唇膏支架。有人评论说："现在是不是任何地方都可以放唇膏了？"
It's actually not for every surface, which, that is a great idea.
其实它并不是适用于所有表面，不过这个想法倒是很不错。
It is a MagSafe, smaller, more compact holder for the lip that snaps on the back of your iPhone.
它其实是一款 MagSafe 小巧紧凑的唇膏支架，可以吸附在 iPhone 背面。
Posted.
发送。
"Hey, Hail," that's really funny because it's such an old school nickname of mine. "
嘿，Hail。"这真的很好笑，因为这是我一个很老派、很久以前的昵称。
"I wonder why you don't launch an SPF. By the way, I love you a lot." "
我很好奇你为什么还没有推出防晒产品。顺便说一句，我特别喜欢你。"
I would love to launch an SPF.
我也非常想推出一款防晒产品。
It's always been in the pipeline for Rhode.
这一直都在 Rhode 的产品规划中。
It just takes a very long time to develop because SPF is very specific, and I'm also very specific about SPF.
只是研发需要很长时间，因为防晒产品要求非常高，而我对防晒产品的要求也非常严格。
But it will come at some point.
不过总有一天会推出的。
Okay, this is a photo I posted in a slide, and it says, "Kendall is unavailable."
好，这是我轮播照片中的一张，上面写着："Kendall 无法接听。"
And someone said, "Why is Kendall's photo a bird? Ha ha." This is not my phone. This is Kylie's phone.
有人评论："为什么 Kendall 的头像是一只鸟？哈哈。"
You would have to ask her why the picture is a bird.
你得去问她为什么头像是一只鸟。
I just thought it was hilarious.
我只是觉得特别搞笑。
It's giving like Kendall's energy.
它特别有 Kendall 的那种感觉。
Okay, this one says, "What sweets did you get? I spy Haribo."
好，这条评论说："你买了哪些零食？我看到 Haribo 了。"
I do love anything sour, like a sour gummy.
我确实特别喜欢所有酸味的零食，比如酸味软糖。
And I did get a lot of sour gummies, and then I got a Dr. Pepper, Dr. Pepper's my favorite soda.
我确实买了很多酸味软糖，还买了一瓶 Dr Pepper，它是我最喜欢的汽水。
And then also, depending on my mood or not, I'd probably get something that has some chocolate involved.
另外，也要看当天心情，我可能还会买一些带巧克力的零食。
But I do remember this night specifically, I just got a bunch of gummies and sour candies.
不过我确实记得那天晚上，我买的基本都是各种软糖和酸味糖果。
It's a picture from my 28th birthday. "We need to know what Hailey's whole chart is." "
这是我28岁生日那天拍的照片。 我们想知道 Hailey 的完整星盘是什么。"
Buckle up, Sagittarius Rising, Sagittarius Sun, and Aries Moon. That's the whole chart, right?
坐稳了：上升射手、太阳射手、月亮白羊。 这就是完整的星盘了，对吧？
Do I need to elaborate further than that?
我还需要再详细解释吗？
I think that should be pretty self-explanatory for what you're dealing with over here.
我觉得，光这些信息就已经足够说明我是什么样的人了。
[TikTok] TikTok "I wonder if she'd ever consider acting for real. Hailey, please try acting."
[TikTok] “我很好奇她会不会认真考虑去演戏。Hailey，拜托试试演戏吧。"
I don't personally feel passionate about acting.
我个人并没有特别热爱演戏。
I think if a specific fun project came along and I felt really good about who I was working with, I would be open.
如果以后有一个有趣的项目找上门，而且合作对象让我很放心，我会愿意尝试。
I would never be completely closed off to anything.
我不会把任何可能性彻底拒之门外。
"Imagine arriving at Sephora and finding your own makeup brand, a dream." "
想象一下，走进 Sephora 就能看到自己的彩妆品牌，简直就是梦想成真。"
And someone said, "I wonder what it feels like."
有人评论说："真想知道那是什么感觉。"
I mean, it's all been an extremely surreal experience.
我的意思是，这一切都非常梦幻，感觉很不真实。
I think specifically walking into Sephora and seeing yourself in there for your own brand is an extra "pinch me" as a young girl who always shopped at Sephora.
尤其是作为一个从小就在 Sephora 买东西的女孩，如今走进店里看到自己的品牌，那种感觉更像是在说"快掐我一下，我是不是在做梦"。
I do think it was very "Pinch me, pinch me, pinch me" moment.
我真的觉得，那就是一个"快掐我一下"的时刻。
Someone said, "Look at her face. Our girl isn't stressing about you."
有人评论说："看看她的表情，我们的女孩才不会因为你们而焦虑。"
And then someone else says, "She isn't. I love her attitude. How does she stay so strong and calm through it all in her business but also life?"
另一个人回复说："确实不会。我喜欢她的心态。她到底是怎么做到无论事业还是生活，都能一直这么坚强、这么冷静的？"
I would say things still get to me.
我会说，这些事情还是会影响到我。
Things still bother me.
有些事情还是会让我困扰。
I do think it makes it a little bit easier to cope with when you have other people around you and in your life who experience the exact same thing that you do, because having mutual, real understanding of what that feels like, makes you feel less alone in it.
不过我确实觉得，当身边有人经历着和你完全一样的事情时，会更容易面对这一切，因为彼此真正理解那种感受，会让你觉得自己没有那么孤单。
And I have friends who experience really the exact same thing that I do.
我也有一些朋友，他们经历的事情几乎和我一模一样。
I'm married to somebody who experiences it on a crazy level.
而且我的丈夫所经历的程度，比我夸张得多。
So I think to be able to vent about things that are bothering you and being able to connect on that, just makes it a little bit easier.
所以，我觉得能够把困扰自己的事情倾诉出来，并和别人产生共鸣，真的会让一切轻松一些。
[Quora] Quora   "What toner does Hailey Bieber use?"
[Quora] “Hailey Bieber用什么爽肤水？"
I use the Glazing Milk as my toner step.
我把 Glazing Milk 当作爽肤水这一步来使用。
"Does Hailey Bieber use tretinoin?" "Hailey Bieber
会用维A酸吗？"
I do occasionally use tretinoin.
我确实偶尔会用维A酸。
It's very strong for my skin, so I like to find things that are a more gentle vitamin A derivative.
它对我的皮肤来说刺激性比较强，所以我更喜欢寻找一些温和的维生素A衍生物。
"Why doesn't Hailey Bieber [chuckles] make a song?" "
为什么 Hailey Bieber 不出首歌呢？"
Not a singer. Not interested in making a song unless it was, like, for jokes.
我不是歌手。 我对出歌没兴趣，除非只是为了搞笑。
"How many tattoos does Hailey Bieber have?"
"Hailey Bieber身上有多少个纹身？"
I have a lot of little ones.
我有很多小纹身。
So if I had to guesstimate, it's like 20 something, 22, 3.
如果非要我估算的话，大概二十几个吧，二十二、二十三个左右。
I kinda count my hand as one piece.
我的手上的纹身我算作一个整体。
Posted.
发送。
Okay, X."What gem stone is on Hailey Bieber's wedding ring?"
好，接下来是 X（原 Twitter）。"Hailey Bieber的婚戒上镶嵌的是什么宝石？"
This is a diamond.
这是钻石。
Right? That's what we're asking?
对吧？问的是这个吧？
This is a diamond. A very beautiful diamond.
这是钻石，一颗非常漂亮的钻石。
Posted.
发送。
Are Hailey Bieber and Gigi Hadid friends? Also, how did they meet? "
Hailey Bieber和 Gigi Hadid 是朋友吗？她们又是怎么认识的？
Gigi and I are friends, and we met many, many years ago just through modeling and other mutual friends.
Gigi和我是朋友，我们很多很多年前因为做模特以及共同的朋友认识了。
Gigi is a sweetheart and I hit her about mom stuff all the time, and I love her.
Gigi人特别好，我经常因为一些当妈妈的事情联系她，我真的很喜欢她。
"What perfume is Hailey Bieber using these days?" I really love Cosmic 2.0 by Kylie Jenner.
“最近用什么香水？" 我最近特别喜欢 Kylie Jenner 的 Cosmic 2.0。
That has been my scent of choice recently.
那就是我最近最常用、最喜欢的一款香味。
"I wonder how Hailey's pregnancy went." "
我很好奇 Hailey 怀孕期间怎么样。"
I had a really good pregnancy, actually, other than the first two-and-a-half months I was really nauseous.
其实我的整个孕期都很好，只是前两个半月恶心得特别厉害。
It's not morning sickness, it's all-day sickness.
那不是"孕吐晨吐"，而是"一整天都在吐"。
I was dealing with nausea from morning till night.
我从早到晚都在忍受恶心。
Once that subsided, I actually felt really good during my whole pregnancy.
等那些症状缓解之后，我整个孕期都感觉很好。
"How do you buy a gift for someone who has everything?" "
你该怎么给一个什么都不缺的人买礼物？"
I love giving people gifts, and I like being a good gift giver.
我很喜欢送礼物，而且我也喜欢做一个会送礼的人。
I have a lot of people in my life that are really hard to shop for because they could get anything they wanted for themselves.
我身边有很多人都特别难买礼物，因为他们想要什么都可以买给自己。
I think you start to just get creative with people and be like, "Hey, you know, is there anything you need right now?"
我觉得这时候就要发挥一点创意，直接问他们："你最近有没有什么需要的？"
Or you just go really simple and buy them a really good pair of socks.
或者干脆简单一点，送他们一双特别好的袜子。
Posted.
发送。
Okay, that's it from me.
好了，我这边就到这里了。
I'm Hailey Bieber and I'm signing off the internet.
我是 Hailey Bieber，现在我要下线了。